module nine delivering results this is after your sales journey it did it
congratulations you made your sale go realize soon enough that that hurdle is
just the forefront right that's the pre hurdle and there are obviously little
mini hurdles along the way hopefully I helped guide you through some of those
if not you know where to reach us now what how do I deliver results right and
this is all about the planning aspect of it delivery timeline cadence of chatting
with the customer onboarding journey understanding where they are at and then
I guess at the end of that cycle whether it takes one month to fix your service
one day to implement your service you know a year to implement your service you
definitely want to have this review aspect that is going to be right here
right diagnose prioritize implement review and this is a super important cycle that
you want to understand for your customers especially that review part because
whether it goes well or bad you need to understand the why behind it right there
are plenty of tools you can track all of this right as long as you're keeping
diligent notes of everything that you feel is important you'll be able to review
afterwards if you leave all that information up in the air in your head you're
not taking I don't know before and after photos you should obviously you should
document everything by video if possible showcase it through your content all of
these things that should be in the review aspect I haven't even gotten into
content yet but we'll get there as well as manage expectations this is a huge one right
your let's go with a example of a plumbing service okay you run a plumbing service and you're their
expectation might be you're remodeling the entire bathroom you're not doing that right you're not
taking apart the sink you're not taking apart the shower head you were there just to fix the
the leaky bathtub and that was it um they might have asked hey since you're there are you gonna
also help with this no I'm not this is what you hired me for so keep those boundaries whatever that may
be if it's software if it's like a literal I need to go into your home service understand what the
boundaries are at the forefront so you can package your product package your service accordingly control
the communication rhythm it's really difficult especially if you're going international to like
not answer all of your clients right you do always want to be there I'm not saying that I'm saying
understand what is that gold tier package and what is that minimum package differentiate it and understand
that communication is going to be one thing that is um appropriate for each package buffer your timelines
if you think something takes two days it might be a week right if you are um fixing the back end of
their inventory website and it's connected to their crm and it's also connected to a google analytics
platform and their their uh their database is on aws I don't know so many different complicated
things that could be happening for a specific business use case it might actually just take you a day
right but it's important to not say a day you do want to hit those expectations but
if for whatever reason one thing breaks and now you're three days in and you're like well that's
because uh aws was down and I couldn't get in and my my account manager wasn't in this week so
blah blah blah blah customer doesn't care they just understood the timeline you gave them and
you didn't hit expectations so buffer that in it's better to say it's gonna take a week and you deliver
in two days right avoid the over promising just it is better for them to be excited about you know even
that example of it was supposed to take a week and it took three days now they're excited all you did was
frame it at the forefront and that's that like subtle account manager conversation skills uh those
are a little more soft skills this isn't necessarily technical but it's super important to have that
you know that good review right that good portfolio uh are they gonna come back you have repeat customers
right so understand what that experience looks like map out those timelines at the forefront
understand what you know week one like what's gonna happen week one what does it take for you to
facilitate week one right what on the back end needs to happen like uh for the plumber they need to know
what parts to get beforehand right they need to ask the right questions during the sales call so understand
the timeline for all of this so you don't have to go back um to well the sales person said this
and now you have a whole different mess of problems right and whether or not you have a ton of
experience you just need to feel confident mimic your competitors right show micro demos what does this
look like in real life loom is a great tool uh obs another software tool that helps you understand uh
or your customers understand exactly what you're seeing um whatever you have to do to just build your
own self-confidence in these sales conversations in the account management side and actually doing the
thing you said you were going to do um these are all very important i always have one of these
these client onboarding checklists i always even give it to them what is the intake form what do you
need right i need your you are a content creator now i'm trying to make as many examples as possible to
like capture all of your attention short time span right or short attention span send intake form
what do i need from them immediately right what name email do i need their address do i need their
uh login information for facebook i don't know right what do i need from them at the very forefront of
all right they signed on the dotted line now what verify access and assets this is that google drive google
worksheets platform that we had talked about i'm again the content creator and they are the business
what do i need from them maybe they have an idea already in their head um and they're gonna send me
a video here's my google drive link here you go right when is the first time we're gonna call after you
sign is it two days later is it that same day uh are they gonna get an automated email what does that
communication channel look like as soon as they book that service just like i said map out that week
one week two week three week four month three month six right map it out or else uh you'll have to deal
with things on the fly and your customer more importantly will have to deal with things as they come
as opposed to feeling more secure about not only their choice but what's going to happen next reporting
cadence are we going to talk every week every month what happens if i don't get what has been delivered
uh do you like literal analytics reporting do you need that weekly how well did my um i don't know
instagram story of me posting myself with the gym equipment work out what are the uh views um likes
shares what does the engagement look like we would do eventual sales look like what does the instagram to
website conversion rate look like were there were there any booked calls whatever the service might be
um map that out right set up and wins implementation iterate handoff right these are all strategies for
each week that your your customer definitely wants and needs to know uh it'll help your own business to
make it a repeatable system repeatable process um and your customer will feel more secure even if they get
this before uh the sale is closed they'll feel more secure they're no longer thinking should i do this
or not they're thinking oh this is what's going to happen week three i don't know about week three um
what if we change week three instead of optimized performance we can add another creator into the mix
right so mapping out that plan so now they're future thinking they're thinking well week three doesn't
sound right how can we change that now they're not thinking did i should i choose them or should i not
should i go with a different company right their future thinking about you first win plans build momentum
and trust immediately sounds sounds easier than done but you want to have that whole process mapped out
again especially that review portion that buyer's remorse leads to negative reviews and you don't want
that day seven rule that's that first onboarding uh customer onboarding journey first week is really
important examples of fast wins um just collect and understand your customer portfolio so you can
eventually use it in your sales conversations and then define your win right what does success with
teramore.io look like for your business we should have that conversation during the sales call
and that should be implemented within that timeline that we talked about this success
um the success being measured in week two is success being measured in week four or is it both
what does success look like bullet point it out map it out include it in the timeline included in the
sales conversations all of that should be true and here are the key takeaways moving on to
our final module here other than the bonus
you